# Leighana Wood

6805 Sandpiper Dr. • Little Rock, AR 72205 • Phone: (360) 827-1325 • E-Mail: Leighana.wood@gmail.com

#### Dear Sir or Madam:

I am still working on my Bachelors degree but have 15 years of professional office experience, and have worked primarily in hospitals. Additionally, I have 17 years of Customer Service experience. I have worked closely with doctors, assisting their needs in emergent and clinical settings, and have proven myself dependable and competent. Additionally, I was the executive assistant to Jay Baskins, proprietor of Export Marine Inc, where I was responsible for assisting him in the day-to-day operations of the business, coordinating his schedule, maintaining office equipment, company website, and customer communications.

I have been told that I am a fast learner by every supervisor I have worked with. I also love teaching and helping people and this makes me an outstanding customer service representative. Through out my professional career I have always sought training in additional desk assignments and responsibilities. I enjoy being able to backup my peers when they are in need of help, and love learning new things. I am professional, dependable, tenacious, and a great problem solver.

My previous position was in the University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences Treasurer's Office as an Administrative Analyst and Cashier. I am proficient in my assigned position and in the position of my co-worker. My position in the treasurer's office has allowed me to become proficient in SAP, the hospital's accounting, personnel, and purchasing system.

In November 2016 I accepted a position within UAMS at the university's Institutional Advancement and Foundation Office. There I am responsible for maintaining Entity records within the Advance database (an Ellocin web based database). I also help to maintain the department's website using iModlues content management system. While I enjoy working for UAMS, I am very interested in taking on a career that I can be challenged by, that fits within my degree area, and provides further learning opportunities.

Thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely,

Leighana Wood

## Objective

I am looking for a career that I can grow and be challenged in. I have a service-oriented heart and am looking for a career that will allow me to have a positive impact in my community.

## Experience

Information Specialist, UAMS Institutional Advancement

November 2016 - Current

- Maintaining Entity records within the Advance database.
- Maintain the department's website using iModlues content management system.
- Creating web based interactive Activity, Event, and Donation forms.
- Posting Donations to the foundation including: Cash, Check, Credit Cards, Stocks, Property, and Gifts in kind.

Administrative Analyst, UAMS Treasurer's Office

June 2014 - November 2016

- Posting departmental deposits in SAP via Customer Service Window and Online/Email submissions.
- Verifying funds, checking for Errors, Researching Bank/SAP Discrepancies.
- Compiling Treasurer's Office Personnel's Collective Bank Deposit.
- Documenting, Filing, Scanning, and Maintaining Spreadsheets of all Backup Documents.
- Coordinating secure storage and transportation for all Fiscal Documentation.
- High Volume Customer interaction.
- Maintaining extensive records of Outlook Emails via archive filing.

Executive Assistant, Export Marine Inc.

January 2014 - June 2015

- Coordinating the Schedule & Email of the proprietor.
- High Volume Customer interaction.
- Database & spreadsheet maintenance.
- Faxing, Scanning, Filing, Advertising.
- Website design and maintenance.

July 2013 - June 2014 I took a year off work to spend time with Family, Move to Arkansas from Washington State, Enroll in UALR's Computer Science B.S. Program and Establish my roots in the Little Rock community.

Financial Counselor, Providence St. Peter Hospital

May 2011 - July 2013

- Assisting un and under- insured Patients find free Services, State Programs, Private insurance, and financial aid through Providence's Charity Care program.
- Gathering required Documentation of Financial Need (Bank info, Property assessments, Income verification, etc.) for processing Charity Care applications, Noting Patient Accounts, Collecting Payments, making Payment Arrangements, Posting Discounts & Payments to their accounts.
- Managing petty cash drawer of \$5,250.00. Processing and providing petty cash Reimbursements to hospital departments.
- Customer Service, Employee Training, Maintaining office equipment.

## Education

UALR, Web Design and Development B.A. Program

2013 - current

I am currently working toward a B.S. in Computer Science. While able to devote all of my attention to school I maintained a 4.0 GPA with 100% in all classes. As I have gone back to work I am no longer able to boast a 100% average, but I have been able to make both the Dean's and Chancellor's list. I am working toward getting back to a 100% as I find the balance between work and school. I am a quick learner, and always enjoy taking on and learning new things, which makes all of this possible.

Naselle Grays-River Valley High School

1998-2002

### **Skills**

I am well versed in SAP and financial processes at UAMS. I have vast experience working with policies that have strict requirements and guidelines. I have worked in Customer Service positions since 2000 and in an office/administrative assistant setting since 2003, and enjoy helping and teaching others. I have strong computer and origination skills. I multitask well and can work thoroughly even when there are multiple interruptions. I have created and implemented policies, written training materials and procedures. I am a quick learner and very adaptable. I am dependable and am proud to be considered a responsible individual by those I have worked for in the past.

My Education in Computer Science and Web Design and Development has given me a plethora of problem solving skills as well as an eye for design. I have learned Coding in C++, Java, JavaScript, Assembly Language, HTML, and CSS. I have had the opportunity to learn the ins and outs of the full Adobe Creative Suite, and feel confident in all general Mac and Windows programs.